AIDAN WALSH

PROGRAMMING INTERNSHIP

PROFILE

I am an enthusiastic and dedicated CG and Technical Artist with three years of University training experience within Arts and Media. I pride myself on being a highly creative individual whom is always striving to learn new skills, develop my current skills and push creative boundaries. I am able to work as a part of a team, whilst also being able to work well on my own initiative.

I have recently enrolled with Code Institude, working towards acheiving a Level 5 Diploma in Full Stack Developing. I have a lot of experience with programming procedural generators, enabling the development team to work efficiently in game engines. I am currently gaining experience working with different declarative and imperative languages such as SQL, JavaScript, C++, C# and Python.

I am currently seeking an internship to gain valuable life skills and work experience in coding to push myself to learn and experience new aspects of the digital industry. The technical knowledge I have gained over the years in Animation and Game Development stand me in good stead to branch out further into other IT and digital sectors.

EXPERIENCE

2020 - Present Alchemy Games Limited

Technical Artist

Working as part of the team behind their latest intellectual property. Approaching CG modelling and Technical Arts such as creating simulations for the VFX.

2019 - 2020 Class A Entertainment

Omerta, Technical Director

Procedural, Environmental & Lighting Artist.

2019 ViacomCBS Domestic Media Networks - Nickelodeon

Valletta, Matla

Volenteered to work internationally with an amazing, friendly crew to help organise and maintain the Nickelodeon Treasure Hunt Malta festival that took place in 2019,

all the way over in Valletta, Malta.

EDUCATION

Present Full Stack Development

Code Institute

Currently enrolled with Code Institute, training to become a Full Stack Developer and

working towards my Level 5 Diploma.

2017 - 2020 **Animation**

University of Salford, Greater Manchester

2:1 BA (Hons) Animation Graduate

CONTACT

★ Warrington, England

28th March 1999

**** 07984 608854

■ aidancgart@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/aidancgart/

www.instagram.com/imaliengod/